{
    "subject": "resource/Mrs_Henderson_Presents",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of Mrs. Henderson Presents is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9465327858924866,
            "question": "What language is Mrs. Henderson Presents spoken in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8680827021598816,
            "question": "What type of film is likely Mrs. Henderson Presents if it is spoken in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8427731990814209,
            "question": "Would someone learning English find Mrs. Henderson Presents helpful?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8236598968505859,
            "question": "What language would subtitles be provided in for a non-English speaker watching Mrs. Henderson Presents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.803210973739624,
            "question": "Is the language of Mrs. Henderson Presents a common one worldwide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7998467683792114,
            "question": "Could someone who only speaks English understand Mrs. Henderson Presents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.481532484292984,
            "question": "Is Mrs. Henderson Presents a foreign film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46706753969192505,
            "question": "Would someone who speaks Spanish need subtitles to understand Mrs. Henderson Presents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1038099154829979,
            "question": "Are there any other languages used in the film besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05263523384928703,
            "question": "What are some other examples of films spoken in English?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Mrs. Henderson Presents is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7924_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other languages used in the film besides English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7924_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would someone who speaks Spanish need subtitles to understand Mrs. Henderson Presents?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7924_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mrs. Henderson Presents a foreign film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7924_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7924_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the musical \"Mrs. Henderson Presents\", including its plot, cast, and reception. There is no explicit mention of the language used in the musical, but it can be inferred that English is the language being used, given that the story is set in London and features a British cast and crew."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that the musical \"Mrs Henderson Presents\" has been performed and discussed primarily within British and Canadian theater settings, with actors delivering their performances in English, which supports the statement that the language of \"Mrs. Henderson Presents\" is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}